getsecuredfiles.com 2015-08-22

# GetPortal CDN Network - Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

Copyright (c) 2013-2015, GetPortal 

All rights reserved. 

We are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. We never fully distribute, share, sell, or rent names, email addresses, or any other personally identifiable information of our users to any third party. This privacy policy outlines our general policy and practices for the types of information GetPortal gathers, how we use it and the notice and choice affected individuals have regarding our use of and their ability to correct that information. 

### GetPortal Privacy & Security Policy

GetPortal will not sell, rent, or give away any of your personal information without your consent. It is our overriding privacy principle that any personal information you provide to us is personal and private. We do not presume that you are granting us permission to share your personal information with third parties wanting to sell you services or products that you have not requested or agreed to. In order to provide you with some of the services, we may need to provide information you supply us to external parties. When this is necessary we will provide you explicit notice and the ability to opt-out. GetPortal and services are not intended for, or designed to attract, individuals under the age of 18. GetPortal does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 18. 

### PERSONS TO WHOM THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES

This privacy policy applies to visitors to our websites, the websites of our partners, affiliates, or other third-parties, the access to which was gained through GetPortal's services; users of GetPortal’s services; and information we collect from visitors or users. The websites of our partners, affiliates, or other third-parties, the access to which was gained through GetPortal's services, may have their own Privacy Policies and may not be covered by GetPortal’s policy. We encourage visitors to these third party websites to make themselves aware of their privacy policies. 

### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

You have to be aware about the fact that GetPortal does not knowingly collect any personal data that can identify a user, such as e-mail, name, gender, age, login names, telephone numbers, address and passwords or any other self-identifying information (hereinafter referred to as the "Personal Information"). GetPortal reserves the right to use cookies on the Site. GetPortal may automatically receive and save some non-personally identifiable information at its server, such as logs from the user's browser, including IP-address, type of browser, internet service provider (ISP), cookie, other technical data and the webpage that is being visited. GetPortal collects non-personally identifiable information only for general purposes, including but not limited to tracking user movements, administering the site, analyzing trends, conducting research and overall improvement of the users’ experience with our web site. 

### COOKIES

Our site uses "cookies" in order to provide a better service to our users. Cookies are placed by your browser on your computer's hard drive to assign a unique identification for your computer. GetPortal does not store information that is considered personal or private in a cookie. This eliminates the chance of other sites reading our cookies and learning your personal or private information, without permission. For instance, we may use cookies to help direct you to the appropriate part of our web site, by indicating that you are a repeat visitor to our site. We also may use that information to present you with services which are easy-to-use and customized to your preferences. We do this in order to track visitors, to reduce the chance of blocking legitimate users, and to provide customized services. 

### THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

The GetPortal may contain links to other sites. Those sites are not under our control; therefore, we make no representations as to the accuracy or integrity of their content. When you access a non-GetPortal web site, you do so at your own risk, and our inclusion of such links does not imply that we endorse or accept any responsibility for their content or use. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of those web sites as well. 

### DATA SECURITY, DATA INTEGRITY, AND ACCESS

GetPortal takes all reasonable steps to protect our users' information from loss, misuse, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure such information. GetPortal only processes users’ information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected by the individual.

### CHANGES OF POLICY

GetPortal reserves the right to revise this Policy from time to time. GetPortal will post the revised Policy on its Site, so that users can constantly be aware of what kind of information GetPortal collects, in what way the information is used and according to what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

### Log Files

GetPortal uses IP-addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. The IP-addresses collected are never linked to personally identifiable information.

### Additional Information

While our web site may be accessed from countries around the world and contains references to GetPortal products, services, and programs, such references do not obligate us to provide such products, services, or programs in every country. 

If you have any questions or feedback about this privacy statement or any other practices of our site, please email us at: support@getportal.net.

By downloading any of the materials contained anywhere on GetPortal, you agree to the terms and provisions outlined in our legal notices section. 

Date of last revision October 14, 2014
